The most important attribute I have built through this
process is the mental.
Because the mental is in a way the foundation
for everything else that I have aimed for.
My editing, training, it depends on the mentality you have.
I didn't really have any structure, I didn't have
any plan, I didn't have any routine that I
followed.
It took a big mental fall, and it also
limited me to achieve my academic dream,
which was to achieve a grade of 11.8.
I didn't have any way, I didn't have any structure.
And what you did was to build my mentality
up, structured from the bottom up.
Now I'm much more effective, now I have more
time with my family, now I have a better
mental health.
And I feel healthy, both mentally, physically and spiritually.